Kraushaar Galleries
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Incoming Letters, circa 1901-1944, Series 2:; (boxes 10-26; 16.25 ft.)
  - L-M, General, undated (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Pyle, William Scott, undated (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - R-S, General, undated (Box 10, Folder 7)
    (Vernon Smith)
  - Van Vleet Tompkins, Frank undated (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - W, General, undated (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Reed, Lloyd G., 1901 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Brissaud, Pierre, 1906 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - A-Z, General, 1913 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    (George Luks)
  - A-Z, General, 1915-1916 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    (only item from 1915 is an envelope addressed by Guy Pène Du Bois)
  - A-Z, General, 1917 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    (Ruth Merrington)
  - Webb, Anne R., and Caroline Webb, 1917 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - A-Z, General, 1918 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    (George Luks; Anne R. Webb)
  - A-Z, General, 1919 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - A-Z, General, 1920 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    (news clipping concerning a gift of an A. L. Bouche pastoral, Evening at St. Aulde, from John F. Kraushaar to the Milwaukee Art Institute)
  - A-Z, General, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    (Maurice Prendergast; John Sloan)
  - A-Z, General, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    (Paul Bartlett; Maurice Prendergast)
  - A-Z, General, undated (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - A-Z, General, 1924 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    (? Fuchs; George Harvey; George Luks; Ruth Merrington)
  - Illegible and Unidentified, 1925 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - A, General, 1925 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    (Galerie J. Allard)
  - Art Institute of Chicago, 1925 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    (Maurice Prendergast exhibition)
  - Ba-Be, General, 1925 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    (Gifford Beal; Reynolds Beal; Emma Louise Story Bellows)
  - Bi-Bu, General, 1925 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    (Cleopatra Bourdelle; Brooklyn Museum)
  - Brouse, W. H., 1925 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Ca-Ch, General, 1925 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Ci-Cu, General, 1925 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Cleveland Museum of Art, 1925 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - D, General, 1925 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Davies, Turner & Co., 1925 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - E, General, 1925 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - F, General, 1925 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - G, General, 1925 (Box 10, Folder 36)
    (Emile Gauguin offering for sale paintings by Paul Gauguin; George A. Gay; William J. Glackens; Philip Becker Goetz)
  - Wm. E. Goodridge & Son, 1925 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - H, General, 1925 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - I, General, 1925 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - J, General, 1925 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - K, General, 1925 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - L, General, 1925 (Box 10, Folder 42)
    (Gaston Lachaise; Lefèvre Galleries)
  - M, General, 1925 (Box 10, Folder 43)
    (Macbeth Gallery; Ruth Merrington)
  - N, General, 1925 (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - O, General, 1925 (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - P, General, 1925 (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Phillips, Duncan, 1925 (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - Q, General, 1925 (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - R, General, 1925 (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - S, General, 1925 (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - Seachrest, Effie, 1925 (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - T, General, 1925 (Box 10, Folder 52)
    (Augustus Vincent Tack; letter from Abigail Brown Tompkins illustrated with a watercolor)
  - U, General, 1925 (Box 10, Folder 53)
  - V, General, 1925 (Box 10, Folder 54)
  - W, General, 1925 (Box 10, Folder 55)
    (Wadsworth Atheneum; L. B. Williams)
  - Watson, William R., 1925 (Box 10, Folder 56)
    (Watson Art Galleries in Montreal)
  - X-Y-Z, General, 1925 (Box 10, Folder 57)
  - Miscellaneous Notes, 1925 (Box 10, Folder 58)
  - Receipts, 1925 (Box 10, Folder 59)
  - A, General, 1926 (Box 10, Folder 60)
    (Art Association of Montreal)
  - Art Institute of Chicago, 1926 (Box 10, Folder 61)
  - Ba-Be, General, 1926 (Box 10, Folder 62)
  - Bi-Bo, General, 1926 (Box 10, Folder 63)
  - Br-Bu, General, 1926 (Box 10, Folder 64)
    (Paul Burlin)
  - Ca-Cl, General, 1926 (Box 10, Folder 65)
    (California Palace of the Legion of Honor; Carnegie Institute)
  - Co-Cu, General, 1926 (Box 10, Folder 66)
  - Cleveland Museum of Art, 1926 (Box 10, Folder 67)
  - D, General, 1926 (Box 10, Folder 68)
  - Davies, Turner & Co., 1926 (Box 10, Folder 69)
  - E, General, 1926 (Box 10, Folder 70)
    (Gordon C. Edwards)
  - F, General, 1926 (Box 10, Folder 71)
  - G, General, 1926 (Box 10, Folder 72)
    (George A. Gay; Edith Glackens)
  - Wm. E. Goodridge & Son, 1926 (Box 10, Folder 73)
  - Ha-He, General, 1926 (Box 10, Folder 74)
  - Hi-Hu, General, 1926 (Box 10, Folder 75)
  - I, General, 1926 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - J, General, 1926 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Chester H. Johnson Galleries, 1926 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - K, General, 1926 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - L, General, 1926 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    (Gaston Lachaise; Ernest Lawson)
  - M, General, 1926 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    (Lucia McBride; Ruth Merrington)
  - N, General, 1926 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - O, General, 1926 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - P, General, 1926 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    (Duncan Phillips; Marjorie Phillips; William Julius Polk)
  - R, General, 1926 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    (Helen M. Robins)
  - Alex. Reid & Lefèvre, Ltd., 1926 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Albert Roullier Art Galleries, 1926 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    (Hugh Dunbar)
  - Sa-Sc, General, 1926 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    (Henry E. Schnakenberg)
  - Se-Sw, General, 1926 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Seachrest, Effie, 1926 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - T, General, 1926 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    (Augustus Vincent Tack; Anna Heyward Taylor)
  - U, General, 1926 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - V, General, 1926 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Wa-We, General, 1926 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    (Wadsworth Atheneum; Watson Art Galleries)
  - Wh-Wy, General, 1926 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    (Lewis B. Williams)
  - X-Y-Z, General, 1926 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    ([William] Zorach)
  - Miscellaneous Notes, 1926 (Box 11, Folder 22-23)
    (catalog for a December watercolor exhibition; lists of C. R. W. Nevinson etchings)
  - Receipts, 1926 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Ac-Am, General, 1927 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - An-As, General, 1927 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    (Anderson Galleries; Art Institute of Chicago; Associated Dealers in American Paintings)
  - Ba-Ben, General, 1927 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Ber-Bre, General, 1927 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Bro-By, General, 1927 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    (Carl W. Broemel; Paul Burlin)
  - C, General, 1927 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    (Carnegie Institute enclosing a letter to John Sloan praising work on display at Kraushaar Galleries; Casson Galleries; Columbus Gallery of Fine Art)
  - Cannell & Chaffin, Inc., 1927 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Cleveland Museum of Art, 1927 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - D, General, 1927 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Davies, Turner & Co., 1927 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - E, General, 1927 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - F, General, 1927 (Box 11, Folder 36)
    (Ferargil Galleries; Fine Arts Gallery of San Diego)
  - G, General, 1927 (Box 11, Folder 37)
    (hand-painted Christmas card from an unidentified correspondent filed under G; George A. Gay; William J. Glackens; Lucy S. Greene)
  - Gage, George E., 1927 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Wm. E. Goodridge & Son, 1927 (Box 11, Folder 39-40)
  - H, General, 1927 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - John Hanna, Inc., 1927 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Harrison, Preston, 1927 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - I, General, 1927 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - J, General, 1927 (Box 11, Folder 45)
    (Thomas Benedict Jonss)
  - Chester H. Johnson Galleries, 1927 (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - K, General, 1927 (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - M. Knoedler & Co., 1927 (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - L, General, 1927 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    (Gaston Lachaise; William F. Laporte)
  - M, General, 1927 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    (Merchants Association of New York; Ruth Merrington)
  - McKean, Margarett Sargent, 1927 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Milwaukee Art Institute, 1927 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    (Mathieu Verdilhan exhibition)
  - N, General, 1927 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - O, General, 1927 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Pa-Po, General, 1927 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    (Howard Ashman Patterson; Portland Art Association)
  - Pr-Py, General, 1927 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    (Leona Prasse; Charles Prendergast)
  - Phillips, Duncan, 1927 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    (exhibitions Phillips has held and his opinions of various artists)
  - Polk, William Julius, 1927 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Q, General, 1927 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - R, General, 1927 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Alex. Reid & Lefèvre, Ltd., 1927 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Albert Roullier Art Galleries, 1927 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Sa-Se, General, 1927 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    (Rudolf H. Sauter; Henry E. Schnakenberg)
  - Sh-Sp, General, 1927 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    (photo postcard of Benito Mussolini from Theodore Sizer; Dolly Sloan; H. S. Southam)
  - St-Sy, General, 1927 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    (A. Suzor-Cote)
  - T, General, 1927 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - U, General, 1927 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - V, General, 1927 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    (Frank Van Vleet Tompkins; Mathieu Verdilhan)
  - Wa-We, General, 1927 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Wh-Wr, General, 1927 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Watson Art Galleries, 1927 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Williams, L. B., 1927 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - X-Y-Z, General, 1927 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Miscellaneous Notes, 1927 (Box 12, Folder 26-27)
  - Receipts, 1927 (Box 12, Folder 28-29)
  - Ab-An, General, 1928 (Box 12, Folder 30)
    (American Art Association; American Federation of Arts)
  - Ar-At, General, 1928 (Box 12, Folder 31)
    (Art Association of Indianapolis; Arts Club of Chicago)
  - Art Institute of Chicago, 1928 (Box 12, Folder 32)
    (Eighth International Watercolor Exhibition)
  - Ba, General, 1928 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Be-Br, General, 1928 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Bu-By, General, 1928 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Ca-Cl, General, 1928 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Co-Cu, General, 1928 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Cannell and Chaffin, Inc., 1928 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Casson Galleries, 1928 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Chase National Bank, 1928 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Cleveland Museum of Art, 1928 (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - D, General, 1928 (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Davies, Turner & Co., 1928 (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - E, General, 1928 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - F, General, 1928 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    (John Duncan Fergusson with a catalog of his exhibition; Findlay Galleries, Inc.; Fine Arts Gallery of San Diego)
  - Ferargil Galleries, 1928 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - G, General, 1928 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    (George A. Gage; Elisabeth C. Geissbuhler concerning an exhibition of work by her husband, Arnold Geissbuhler; Lucy S. Greene)
  - J. J. Gillespie & Co., 1928 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Wm. E. Goodridge & Son, 1928 (Box 13, Folder 6-7)
  - Ha, General, 1928 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - He-Hu, General, 1928 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Harrison, Preston, 1928 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - I, General, 1928 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Internal Revenue Service, 1928 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - J, General, 1928 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Chester H. Johnson Galleries, 1928 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - K, General, 1928 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - M. Knoedler & Co., 1928 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - La-Le, General, 1928 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Li-Ly, General, 1928 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Ma-Mc, General, 1928 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    (Macbeth Gallery)
  - Me-My, General, 1928 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - McKean, Margarett Sargent, 1928 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - N, General, 1928 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Northwood, J. E., 1928 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - O, General, 1928 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - P, General, 1928 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    (Walter Pach discussing his book Ananias; or, the False Artist; Leona Prasse)
  - Phillips, Duncan, and Marjorie Phillips, 1928 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Q, General, 1928 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - R, General, 1928 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    (Albert Roullier Art Galleries)
  - Alex. Reid & Lefèvre, Ltd., 1928 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Sa-Sm, General, 1928 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    (B. D. Saklatwalla; Rudolf H. Sauter concerning an exhibition; John Sloan with a press release from Kraushaar Galleries announcing sale of 32 Sloan paintings to a private collector)
  - So-Sy, General, 1928 (Box 13, Folder 31)
    (H. S. Southam; Joseph Stella)
  - Seachrest, Effie, 1928 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Southam, H. S., 1928 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - T, General, 1928 (Box 13, Folder 34)
    (Augustus Vincent Tack; Toledo Museum of Art)
  - U, General, 1928 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - V, General, 1928 (Box 13, Folder 36)
    (Vassar College; Mathieu Verdilhan)
  - W, General, 1928 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - X-Y-Z, General, 1928 (Box 13, Folder 38)
    (William Zorach)
  - Miscellaneous Notes, 1928 (Box 13, Folder 39-40)
    (catalog for a William J. Glackens exhibition in March)
  - Receipts, 1928 (Box 13, Folder 41-42)
  - Al-Am, General, 1929 (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - An-Ar, General, 1929 (Box 13, Folder 44)
    (Arts Club of Chicago)
  - Ba-Be, General, 1929 (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - Bi-Bu, General, 1929 (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - Ca, General, 1929 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Ch-Cu, General, 1929 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    (Cleveland Museum of Art concerning its Sixth Annual Exhibition of Watercolors and Pastels)
  - Chase National Bank, 1929 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - D, General, 1929 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Davies, Turner & Co., 1929 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - E, General, 1929 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - F, General, 1929 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - G, General, 1929 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Gage, George E., 1929 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Gay, George A., 1929 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Wm. E. Goodridge & Son, 1929 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - H, General, 1929 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Harrison, Preston, 1929 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - I, General, 1929 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - J, General, 1929 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Chester H. Johnson Galleries, 1929 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - K, General, 1929 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - L, General, 1929 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - M, General, 1929 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - N, General, 1929 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - O, General, 1929 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - P, General, 1929 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    (Walter Pach; Howard Ashman Patterson; Duncan Phillips)
  - R, General, 1929 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - S, General, 1929 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Southam, H. S., 1929 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - T, General, 1929 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - U, General, 1929 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - V, General, 1929 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    (H. Verdilhan)
  - W, General, 1929 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - X-Y-Z, General, 1929 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Miscellaneous Notes, 1929 (Box 14, Folder 31-32)
    (catalogs for exhibitions of work by Arnold Friedman, Adriaan Lubbers, and Margarett Sargent McKean)
  - Bills, 1929 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Receipts, 1929 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Illegible,, 1930 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - A, General, 1930 (Box 14, Folder 36)
    (American Art Dealers Association with minutes from the fall meeting)
  - Art Institute of Chicago, 1930 (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - B, General, 1930 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Ca-Ch, General, 1930 (Box 14, Folder 39)
    (Carnegie Institute regarding its 29th international exhibition)
  - Ci-Cu, General, 1930 (Box 14, Folder 40)
    (College Art Association)
  - Chase National Bank, 1930 (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - Cleveland Museum of Art, 1930 (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - D, General, 1930 (Box 14, Folder 43)
    (Bernard Boutet de Monvel; Guy Pène Du Bois)
  - Davies, Turner & Co., 1930 (Box 14, Folder 44)
  - E, General, 1930 (Box 14, Folder 45)
  - F, General, 1930 (Box 14, Folder 46)
  - Furthman, Jules, 1930 (Box 14, Folder 47)
  - G, General, 1930 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    (attorneys Garfield and Seligson concerning legal rights to sculpture by Gaston Lachaise)
  - J. J. Gillespie & Co., 1930 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Wm. E. Goodridge & Son, 1930 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - H, General, 1930 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Harrison, Preston, 1930 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - I, General, 1930 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    (Independent Gallery in London)
  - J, General, 1930 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - K, General, 1930 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - L, General, 1930 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - M, General, 1930 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - N, General, 1930 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - O, General, 1930 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - P, General, 1930 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    (Walter Pach; Howard Ashman Patterson concerning financial matters)
  - R, General, 1930 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Alex. Reid & Lefèvre, Ltd., 1930 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - S, General, 1930 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Southam, H. S., 1930 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - T, General, 1930 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    (Helen Toulgouat; Harold M. Tovell)
  - U, General, 1930 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - V, General, 1930 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - W, General, 1930 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - X-Y-Z, General, 1930 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Miscellaneous Notes, 1930 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Bills, 1930 (Box 15, Folder 24-25)
  - Receipts, 1930 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Ac-Am, General, 1931 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    (Albright Art Gallery)
  - An-Ar, General, 1931 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - American Art Dealers Association, 1931 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Art Institute of Chicago, 1931 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - B, General, 1931 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Ca-Ch, General, 1931 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Ci-Cu, General, 1931 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - College Art Association, 1931 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - D, General, 1931 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Davies, Turner & Co., 1931 (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - E, General, 1931 (Box 15, Folder 37)
    (Dolly Sloan with Exposition of Indian Tribal Arts, Inc.)
  - F, General, 1931 (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - Furthman, Jules, 1931 (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - G, General, 1931 (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - Wm. E. Goodridge & Son, 1931 (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - H, General, 1931 (Box 15, Folder 42)
    (Harlow, McDonald & Company)
  - Harrison, Preston, 1931 (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - I, General, 1931 (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - J, General, 1931 (Box 15, Folder 45)
    (Erle Johnson)
  - K, General, 1931 (Box 15, Folder 46)
    (Tud Kempf)
  - L, General, 1931 (Box 15, Folder 47)
  - M, General, 1931 (Box 15, Folder 48)
    (records of loans to Museum of Modern Art)
  - McClees Galleries, 1931 (Box 15, Folder 49)
    (John Sloan exhibition)
  - N, General, 1931 (Box 15, Folder 50)
  - O, General, 1931 (Box 15, Folder 51)
  - Pa-Ph, General, 1931 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    (Walter Pach; Pennsylvania Museum of Art; Henri Petiet)
  - Pi-Py, General, 1931 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    (L. R. Pissarro concerning research for a catalog of oil paintings, pastels, and gouaches by Camille Pissarro)
  - R, General, 1931 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    (Rhode Island School of Design)
  - Sa-Se, General, 1931 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    (Edmond Sagot; illustrated letter from Rudolf H. Sauter; Henry E. Schnakenberg)
  - Sh-Sy, General, 1931 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    (W. Scott & Sons; Dolly Sloan; John Sloan; Joseph Stella)
  - T, General, 1931 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    (Augustus Vincent Tack; Helen Toulgouat concerning artwork by her husband, Pierre)
  - V, General, 1931 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - W, General, 1931 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - X-Y-Z, General, 1931 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous Notes, 1931 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    (Catalogue of the Complete Collection of Etchings by John Sloan, January 1, 1927; invitation list and catalog for a Walter Pach exhibition)
  - Bills and Receipts, 1931 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - A, General, 1932 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    (American Art Dealers Association with meeting minutes)
  - Art Institute of Chicago, 1932 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - B, General, 1932 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    (Gifford Beal; illustrated postcard from Reynolds Beal)
  - C, General, 1932 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Cleveland Museum of Art, 1932 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - College Art Association, 1932 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - D, General, 1932 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    (Randall Davey; Nicholas A. Donnelly concerning the Kraushaar family estate; Guy Pène Du Bois)
  - E, General, 1932 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - F, General, 1932 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - G, General, 1932 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    (Goodman-Walker, Inc.)
  - Wm. E. Goodridge & Son, 1932 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - H, General, 1932 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - I, General, 1932 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - J, General, 1932 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - K, General, 1932 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - L, General, 1932 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - M, General, 1932 (Box 16, Folder 28)
    (Macbeth Gallery discussing ways to help artists fix prices for the winter season of 1932-1933 and a recent increase in the theft of etchings from galleries)
  - N, General, 1932 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - O, General, 1932 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - P, General, 1932 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - R, General, 1932 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Sa-Sh, General, 1932 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Si-Sy, General, 1932 (Box 16, Folder 34)
    (Dolly Sloan; Syracuse Museum of Fine Arts)
  - T, General, 1932 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - V, General, 1932 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - W, General, 1932 (Box 16, Folder 37)
    (Mildred Williams; Joseph Winterbotham)
  - X-Y-Z, General, 1932 (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Miscellaneous Notes, 1932 (Box 16, Folder 39-40)
    (catalogs for an exhibition of work by Henri de Toulouse-Lautrec; catalog for exhibition of paintings, watercolors, and drawings by various artists)
  - Bills and Receipts, 1932 (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - Ac-Am, General, 1933 (Box 16, Folder 42)
    (American Art Dealers Association)
  - An-Ar, General, 1933 (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - American Federation of Arts, 1933 (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - Art Institute of Chicago, 1933 (Box 16, Folder 45)
  - B, General, 1933 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    (Gifford Beal; Reynolds Beal; illustrated letter from R. B. Bearman)
  - C, General, 1933 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Cleveland Museum of Art, 1933 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - College Art Association, 1933 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    (efforts to establish an artists' cooperative and a lending library to rent works of art on behalf of artists)
  - D, General, 1933 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - E, General, 1933 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - F, General, 1933 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - G, General, 1933 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    (William J. Glackens; Goodman-Walker, Inc.; Marcel Guiot)
  - Wm. E. Goodridge & Son, 1933 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - H, General, 1933 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Harrison, Preston, 1933 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - I, General, 1933 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Chester H. Johnson Galleries, 1933 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - K, General, 1933 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    (Max Kahn; Henry G. Keller)
  - L, General, 1933 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - M, General, 1933 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Macbeth Gallery, 1933 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - N, General, 1933 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    (Nebraska Art Association)
  - O, General, 1933 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - P, General, 1933 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    (George S. Payne; Pennsylvania Museum of Art; Charles Prendergast)
  - Q, General, 1933 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - R, General, 1933 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Sa-So, General, 1933 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    (Henry E. Schnakenberg; John Sloan; Nat Smolin)
  - Sp-Sy, General, 1933 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - T, General, 1933 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - V, General, 1933 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - W, General, 1933 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - X-Y-Z, General, 1933 (Box 17, Folder 28)
    (Yale University; Mahonri Mackintosh Young)
  - Miscellaneous Notes, 1933 (Box 17, Folder 29-30)
  - Receipts, 1933 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - A, General, 1934 (Box 17, Folder 32)
    (American Art Dealers Association; Art Students League of New York)
  - American Federation of Arts, 1934 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Art Institute of Chicago, 1934 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Ba-Bl, General, 1934 (Box 17, Folder 35)
    (Gifford Beal; Reynolds Beal; Henry Block with a photograph of one of Block's paintings)
  - Bo-By, General, 1934 (Box 17, Folder 36)
    (Ann Brockman; Brooklyn Museum)
  - Walter Bull & Sanders, Ltd., 1934 (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - C, General, 1934 (Box 17, Folder 38)
    (City Art Museum of St. Louis; Courvoisier Galleries; Currier Gallery of Art)
  - Carnegie Institute, 1934 (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - College Art Association, 1934 (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - D, General, 1934 (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - E, General, 1934 (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - F, General, 1934 (Box 17, Folder 43)
    (Emma L. Frankenberg)